<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<content>
  <title>Salesforce</title>
  <data>
    <![CDATA[
		<div class="content-header">
            <img src="/content/xml/en/images/salesforce-logo-small.png" alt="" />    
            <button class="k-button" onclick="alert('add link to settings')">INSTALL</button>
        </div>
    
        <p>
            Our Salesforce integration will help your sales and support teams 
            move any relevant chat data to Salesforce with a single click. This will keep your operators updated on 
            previous communication with new and existing clients.
        </p>
        <p>Your agents will also have quick access to the Salesforce information in the chat window.</p>
        <p>Here should be an image with chat window with information from salesforce</p>
    
        <h2>Installation</h2>
        <p>
            In order to install this integration, go through the following steps:
            <ol>
                <li>
                    Login to your <a href="https://login.salesforce.com" target="_blank">Salesforce</a>, and reset you security token.
                </li>
            </ol>
        </p>
        <div class="img-border">
            <img src="/Content/xml/en/images/salesforce-reset-security-token.png" alt="" />
            <!--<center>Pic. 1 Salesforce reset secuirity token page</center>-->
        </div>
        <p>
            Your will receive email with you security token from Salesforce service, like shown on the image below.
        </p>
        
        <div class="img-border">
            <img src="/Content/xml/en/images/salesforce-reset-security-token-email.png" alt="" />
            <!--<center>Pic. 2 Email example form Salesforce service after reseting security token</center>-->
        </div>

        <ol start="2">
            <li>
                Login to the livehelp service and go the the <a href="">Settings Integration section</a>. 
            </li>
            <li>
                Select a Salesforce button and fill the required fields.
            </li>
        </ol>
        
        <div class="img-border">
            <img src="/Content/xml/en/images/salesforce-settings.png" alt="" />
        </div>
        
        <ol start="4">
            <li>
                Also you can set the next options:
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        Add contacts or leads automatically - when chat started a new contact or lead will be added automatically.
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        Send all transcripts automatically - when chat has finished a chat transcript will be added automatically.
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        Send offline messages automatically  - when visitor send offline message it will added to higrise automatically.
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                Press 'Connect' button.
            </li>
        </ol>
        
        <p>
            After checking you credentials, the information about integration will be saved and you will able to get or save info about contacts or leads in Salesforce service. 
        </p>
        
        <h2>Information about visitor in the chat window</h2>
        
        <p>
            When your Salesforce lead or contact starts a chat, he or she will be recognized and the stored information about the lead or contact will be automatically placed in the chat window.
        </p>
        
        <div class="img-border">
            <img src="/content/xml/en/images/salesforce-visitor-details.png" alt=""/>
        </div>
        
        <h2>Adding leads or contacts through chat</h2>

        <p>
            Also you have an ability to add leads or contacts and store chat transcripts manually.
            To add a lead or contact to Salesforce, you need to click on special button in chat window header and then on Add to Salesforce. 
        </p>
        
        <div class="img-border">
            <img src="/content/xml/en/images/salesforce-adding-to.png" alt=""/>
        </div>
        
        <p>
            A special page will be opened where you can create a new lead or contact and attach chat transcript to existing leads or contacts.
        </p>
    </p>
	]]>
  </data>
</content>