<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<content>
  <title>User Roles</title>
  <data>
    <![CDATA[
		<h1>User roles in Livehelp</h1>

        <p>
			Livehelp has three main roles which serve a specific purpose.  These roles are <strong>Agents, Administrators,</strong> and the <strong>Owner</strong>.
        </p>
		
		
        <h2>Agents Role</h2>
        <p>
            Agent is the most frequent role used in Livehelp.  This role will typically be used by your company to provide Live Help to your customers.  Agents have very limited access to Settings and History.
			
			An agent can be added by any <strong>Administrators</strong> or the <strong>Owner</strong> of an account.
			
			<div class="blockquote">
				<i class="fa fa-file-text"></i>
				<p>Avoid sharing accounts between two different agents.  You can create an agent for several employees responsible for chatting with your visitors.</p>
			</div>				
        </p>
		
        <h2>Administrators Role</h2>
        <p>
            Administrators have full control over all settings in Livehelp.  This role will typically be used by your company to act as a team lead for your agents.  
			
			An agent can be added by any <strong>Administrators</strong> or the <strong>Owner</strong> of an account.
			
			<div class="blockquote">
				<i class="fa fa-file-text"></i>
				<p>Typically you only need one Administrator to control an entire team within your organization.  But you can also create multiple administrator roles to delegate tasks in case an Administrator is not available.</p>
			</div>				
        </p>
		
		
		<h2>Owner Role</h2>
        <p>
            Owners have full control over all settings in Livehelp.  There can only be one Owner per Livehelp account.  This role is in charge over all Administrators and Agents within your organization.  
			
			An agent can be added by any <strong>Administrators</strong> or the <strong>Owner</strong> of an account.
			
			<div class="blockquote">
				<i class="fa fa-file-text"></i>
				<p>Only the owner can access billing section and make payments.</p>
			</div>				
        </p>
		
		

	]]>
  </data>
</content>