<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<content>
  <title>Highrise</title>
  <data>
    <![CDATA[
        <div class="content-header">
            <img src="/content/xml/en/images/highrise-logo-small.png" alt="" />    
            <button class="k-button" onclick="alert('add link to settings')">INSTALL</button>
        </div>
        
        <div class="clear"></div>
        <p>
            Integrate your Livehelp chat with Highrise for an easy and effective way of handling your online contacts. 
            This integration will make the following possible:
        </p>

        <ul>
            <li>Adding new and old contacts and deals with one click</li>
            <li>Gathering of contact information using the pre-chat survey data</li>
            <li>Forwarding chat transcripts directly to Highrise and assigning them to contacts</li>
            <li>Displaying contact information in the visitor lists, chat window, recents chats and history</li>
        </ul>

        <p>
            Boost your sales and support activities by keeping your contact information updated with the Highrise integration.
        </p>
            
        <h2>Setting up the integration</h2>
        
        <p>
            In order to enable this integration, follow the steps below:
        </p>

        <ol>
            <li>Go to the <a href="" target="_blank">CRM integration section</a>.</li>
            <li>Click on the Highrise button. You will see the next form:</li>
        </ol>
        
        <div class="img-border">
            <img src="/content/xml/en/images/highrise-settings.png" alt=""/>
        </div>
        
        <ol start="3">
            <li>
                Now, go to your Highrise, select Account & settings and choose My info.
            </li>
        </ol>
        
        <div class="img-border">
            <img src="/content/xml/en/images/highrise-my-info.png" alt=""/>
        </div>
        
        <ol start="4">
            <li>
                Go to the <strong>API token</strong> section and copy your <strong>Authentication token</strong>.
            </li>
        </ol>
        
        <div class="img-border">
            <img src="/content/xml/en/images/highrise-api-token.png" alt=""/>
        </div>
        
        <ol start="5">
            <li>
                Enter your Highrise subdomain and paste the API token.
            </li>
        </ol>
        
        <div class="img-border">
            <img src="/content/xml/en/images/highrise-filled-settings.png" alt=""/>
        </div>
        
        <ol start="6">
            <li>
                Also you can set the next options:
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        Add contacts automatically - when chat started a new contact will be added automatically.
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        Send all transcripts automatically - when chat has finished a chat transcript will be added automatically.
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        Send offline messages automatically  - when visitor send offline message it will added to higrise automatically.
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                Click on 'Connect' button.
            </li>
        </ol>
        
        <p>
            After checking you credentials, the information about integration will be saved and you will able to get or save info about contacts in Highrise service. 
        </p>

        <h2>Information about visitor in the chat window</h2>
        
        <p>
            When your Highrise contact starts a chat, he or she will be recognized and the stored information about the contact will be automatically placed in the chat window.
        </p>
        
        <div class="img-border">
            <img src="/content/xml/en/images/highrise-visitor-details.png" alt=""/>
        </div>
        
        <h2>Adding contacts through chat</h2>

        <p>
            Also you have an ability to add contacts and store chat transcripts manually.
            To add a contact to Highrise, you need to click on special button in chat window header and then on Add to Highrise. 
        </p>
        
        <div class="img-border">
            <img src="/content/xml/en/images/highrise-adding-to.png" alt=""/>
        </div>
        
        <p>
            A special page will be opened where you can create a new contact or attach chat transcript to existing contacts.
        </p>
	]]>
  </data>
</content>