<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<content>
  <title>Desk</title>
  <data>
    <![CDATA[
	    <div class="content-header">
            <img src="/content/xml/en/images/desk-logo-small.png" alt="" />    
            <button class="k-button" onclick="alert('add link to settings')">INSTALL</button>
        </div>
    
        <p>LiveHelp integration with Desk.com web-based service allows you to keep your customer support communication in one place.</p>
    
        <h2>Installation</h2>
    
        <ol start="1">
            <li>
               Login to your <a href="https://login.desk.com" target="_blank">Desk.com</a>
            </li>
            <li>
                After logging in, click on <strong>Agent</strong> in the upper left portion of the page and then select <strong>Admin</strong>.
            </li>
        </ol>
        
        <div class="img-border">
          <img src="/Content/xml/en/images/desk-admin-menu.png" />
        </div>  
    
        <ol start="3">
            <li>
               Next, click on <strong>Settings</strong> in the top right portion of the page. 
            </li>
        </ol>
        
        <div class="img-border">
          <img src="/Content/xml/en/images/desk-settings-link.png" />
        </div>  
    
        <ol start="4">
            <li>
               Proceed to <strong>API</strong> and click on <strong>Add API Application</strong>. 
            </li>
        </ol>
        
        <div class="img-border">
          <img src="/Content/xml/en/images/desk-add-app-button.png" />
        </div>
    
        <ol start="5">
            <li>
               You will need to provide the name of the API Application and a website URL. 
               You can use “Livehelp” as the name and “https://chat.livehelp.com” as website URL. 
               Leave the two remaining spaces blank. 
               When you are done with inputting the info, click on <strong>Add</strong>. 
            </li>
        </ol>
        
        <div class="img-border">
          <img src="/Content/xml/en/images/desk-adding-app.png" />
        </div>
        
        <p>
            This will create an API Application for LiveChat and provide you with a <strong>Key</strong> and an <strong>Access Token</strong>. 
            You will need those in the next step of the guide.
        </p>
        <p>
            Your <strong>Key</strong> and <strong>Secret</strong> can be found on the left, below the name of your newly created API Application. 
        </p>
        <p>
            The <strong>Access Token</strong> can be found on the right under <strong>Your Access Token</strong>. 
        </p>
        <p>
            Clicking on it will bring up your <strong>Token</strong> and <strong>Token Secret</strong>. 
        </p>
        
        <div class="img-border">
          <img src="/Content/xml/en/images/desk-api-token.png" />
        </div>
    
        <ol start="6">
            <li>
               Go to the Desk.com integration page and fill the required fields. 
            </li>
        </ol>
        
        <ol start="7">
            <li>
                Also you can set the next options:
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        Send all transcripts automatically - when chat has finished a chat transcript will be added as case.
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        Send offline messages automatically - when visitor send offline message it will added as case to Desk.
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        Automatically assign cases to the Desk agent with the same email address as the Livehelp agent - case will be assigned to Desk agent.
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ol>
    
        <div class="img-border">
          <img src="/Content/xml/en/images/desk-integration-page.png" />
        </div>    
   
        <ol start="8">
            <li>
                Click 'Connect' button.
            </li>
        </ol>
    
        <p>  
          After checking you credentials, the information about integration will be saved.
        </p>
        
         <h2>Information about visitor in the chat window</h2>
        
        <p>
            When your Desk customer starts a chat, he or she will be recognized and the stored information about the customer will be automatically placed in the chat window.
        </p>
        
        <div class="img-border">
            <img src="/content/xml/en/images/desk-visitor-details.png" alt=""/>
        </div>
        
        <h2>Adding cases through chat</h2>

        <p>
            Also you have an ability to create case with chat transcripts manually.
            For adding a case to Desk, you need to click on special button in chat window header and then on Add to Desk. 
        </p>
        
        <div class="img-border">
            <img src="/content/xml/en/images/desk-adding-to.png" alt=""/>
        </div>
        
        <p>
            A special page will be opened where you can create a case or attach chat transcript to existing customers.
        </p>
    
	]]>
  </data>
</content>